Three weddings. One happy couple.
Confetti is a comedy, romance film directed by Debbie Isitt.
A mockumentary that follows three couples as they battle it out to win
the coveted title of 'Most Original Wedding of the Year'.
Matt, played by Martin Freeman.
Sam (as Jessica Stevenson), played by Jessica Hynes.
Josef, played by Stephen Mangan.
Isabelle, played by Meredith MacNeill.
Michael, played by Robert Webb.
Joanna, played by Olivia Colman.
Confetti is a 2006 British mockumentary romantic
comedy film released on 5 May 2006.
It was conceived and directed by Debbie Isitt and stars many acclaimed British comedians, including Jessica
Stevenson, Jimmy Carr, Martin Freeman, Mark Heap, Julia Davis, Robert Webb and Olivia Colman.
It follows a bridal magazine competition for the most original wedding, the ultimate
prize being a house, and the three couples who are chosen to compete.
The film follows the contestants in a fly-on-the-wall
documentary style, akin to The Office.
The script was entirely improvised.
The film was a box office success, grossing $4.9
million on a budget of $2 million.
The film explores themes of wedding, found footage, woman director, naturism.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.